□+(1)647-973-6640 | ■ andrewsivabalan@gmail.com | □ Cradle0 | □ andrew-sivabalan

Summary_

I am a Math and Computer Science graduate with additive knowledge from my previous Accounting experiences. I have tutored in Math, done basic accounting and fast food retail work. My adeptness developed from the intense problem solving from my undergraduate has prepared me for many challenging tasks.

Skills_

Programming Python, C

Machine Learning Related Frameworks pytorch, sci-kit, jupyter, numpy

Projects

Alice Maze Solver

PYTHON

• Created an algorithm of solve Alice Mazes via BFS (http://www.logicmazes.com/alice.html)

MNIST Label Predictor

Code

PYTHON Oct 2021

· Labeled handwritten digits with classifying techniques such as kNN, logistic regression, Naive Bayes and Gaussian Discriminant.

Internet of Things Gateway Controller and Signal

Coae

Dec 2019

• Created functions to handle messaging and communication between a gateway and controller in an IoT environment.

Parallel Make Program Code

C Nov 2019

• Created a Parallel Make program that parse Makefiles that evaluates and execute with the option of doing so in parallel.

Education

University of Toronto Toronto, Canada

HONOURS BACHELOR OF SCIENCE

Sept. 2015 - Apr. 2022

• Graduated with Distinction - 3.23 cGPA

Brock University St. Catherines, Canada

HONOURS BACHELOR OF ACCOUNTING Sept. 2013 - Dec. 2014

Work Experience _____

Pizzaiolo Toronto, Ontario

CASHIER AND GENERAL BOOKKEEPER

Dec. 2019 - Apr. 2021

- Communicated and served over 50 customers a day at the cashier by preparing their order and managing the line, ensuring a quick and pleasant experience.
- Accounted for general expenses and revenue through Excel spreadsheets to keep track of expenditure and profit and to ensure that future expenditures where for increasing profits and were necessary to the functioning of the business.

Mill Street Brewery

Toronto, Ontario

JUNIOR ACCOUNTANT

Jan. 2015 - Aug. 2015

- Processed on average 200+ customer payments with cheque and credit card reconciliations daily with great accuracy to ensure timely deposits.
- Accounted for inventory and supplies payable daily to prepare payments for by matching invoices with the proper documentation leading to prompt payment.
- Worked multiple terms, summer of 2016 and 2017.